hotkeys.com 2017-04-10

# Privacy Policy | Hotkeys - Providing Superior Traffic Monetization

  1. INTRODUCTION
  2. OUR COMMITMENT
  3. PRIVACY POLICY HIGHLIGHTS
  4. INFORMATION COLLECTION
  5. HOW WE USE, SHARE AND MAINTAIN YOUR INFORMATION
  6. YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES
  7. ADDITIONAL TERMS
  8. CONTACT US

##### INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") describes how Hot Media, Inc. (“Hot Media” or “we” or “us”) collects, uses and shares your information when you use the Hotkeys website or service. Please read the complete Policy below and contact us at legalnotice@rightside.co with any questions. If you are not comfortable with this Policy, do not provide us with any personal information. By using this website or service, you expressly accept this Policy and consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy, including without limitation its transfer to and storage on our servers in the United States or elsewhere in the world.

WE MAY MODIFY OUR POLICY AT ANY TIME. NON-MATERIAL CHANGES AND CLARIFICATIONS WILL TAKE EFFECT IMMEDIATELY; MATERIAL CHANGES WILL TAKE EFFECT 30 DAYS AFTER PROVIDING NOTICE VIA THIS WEBSITE OR THE EMAIL ADDRESS WE HAVE ON FILE FOR YOU. WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO KEEP YOURSELF UP-TO-DATE BY CHECKING THIS POLICY AT LEAST EVERY 30 DAYS. THE LATEST MODIFICATION DATE WILL BE DISPLAYED AT THE TOP OF THE POLICY.

##### OUR COMMITMENT

This Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our sites and our products and services offered through our sites. Hot Media is committed to industry self-regulation and strives to assure disclosure of our privacy practices to make our data practices transparent for our users. Realizing that each user has specific concerns and needs, we also seek to give you ways to manage your own level of privacy by offering you choices and by continuing to educate both you and ourselves on Internet privacy issues.

##### PRIVACY POLICY HIGHLIGHTS

This section highlights the key takeaways from our Policy, but you should also read the full text of our Policy.

**Personal Information:** We use the term “personal information” to describe information that is associated with a specific person and is used to directly identify that person. We collect personal information about you when you voluntarily disclose or authorize the disclosure of such information to us (such as by registering an account or posting on our forums). 

**Information Uses:** We may use your personal information to communicate with you, run and improve our services and website, personalize content, and ensure compliance with the law.

**Information Sharing:** We do not knowingly disclose personal information that we collect from you to third parties other than our affiliated companies unless you consent to such transfer, or in the limited circumstances where such information is provided to a third party performing services for us under an obligation of confidentiality, in connection with a transfer of all or part of our business or assets, and for legal or regulatory compliance and safety purposes.

**Your Choices:** You can manage your privacy by editing your information on your account, opting out of emails and certain interest-based advertising, and turning off cookies in your browser.

Contact us by email at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co).

##### PRIVACY POLICY

##### 1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION

**Information You Provide To Us.**

We collect information you provide to us through the registration process on our website. We may also collect any information, including personal information, you post on any public areas of our website, like comments or forums, or that you may give us in any other way (such as through an email or survey) . Please note that we are not responsible for any personal information you post in public areas. Since information you post to public areas of our website is not considered private information, we may also feature your posted content, such as reviews or comments, on our website.

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from any children under 13 or allow them to register on our website or use our services. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without her parent’s or guardian’s consent, please contact us at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co).

**Other Information We Collect From You.**

In addition to the information you provide to us by registering an account or posting content on our website, we also collect information through the use of cookies and pixel tags. We also use cookies and other technologies to gather information about your use of our website so that we may give you a personalized experience of our website and help us understand how users are using our services.

**Cookies.**

When you visit our website, we may send one or more "cookies" – small data files – to your computer to uniquely identify your browser to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the sites. We use persistent, identifying cookies to remember your information, such as your preferences and login information. Our cookies do not collect personal information that you provide during the account registration process, but they do collect other information such as the following:

  * Your computer's IP address and information about its operating system or platform (Mac, Windows XP, etc.), browser type, and browser language setting;
  * URL of the last webpage you visited before arriving at our website;
  * The date and time you access our website and pages you visit;
  * Demographic and other non-personally identifiable profile information about you;
  * Your activity on our website (such as your clicks, pages viewed, comments, search results selected, etc.); and
  * Information to combat fraud or misuse.

For more information about cookies and how to manage them, please see the section below labeled Your Privacy Choices.

**Pixel Tags.**

Also known as a web beacon or clear GIF, a pixel tag is a tiny graphic with a unique identifier embedded invisibly on a webpage (or an online ad or email). We may use pixel tags to measure the number of clicks on certain pages or sections of our website.

**Information Collected by Third Parties.**

Our website and services includes links to websites and other content from third party businesses. We do not provide any personal information to these third-party websites, or other businesses.

If you click a link to visit another website or use the third-party referral service available on our websites or services, you will be subject to that website or provider’s privacy policy. This Policy only applies to information collected on website or through the Hotkeys service. You may also be asked to provide personal information or permit the transfer to a third party in connection with promotions, sweepstakes or contests we host. If you are not willing to share the information with such third parties, do not participate in such promotions, sweepstakes or contests.

##### 2\. HOW WE USE, SHARE AND MAINTAIN YOUR INFORMATION

**Information Uses.**

We use your personal information to respond to your requests, personalize our service, administer our website, communicate with registered users, enforce our rights and the rights of third parties, and investigate and ensure compliance with our Terms of Service and applicable law. We use non-personal information (such as demographic information, anonymous usage data, IP address, web browser information, referring/exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, etc.) to help us understand how our users are using our website or services and in turn make our website and more useful to you.

**Information Sharing.**

We share your personal information if authorized by you or in the limited instances described below. We may be subject to liability in cases of onward transfer to third parties that do not conform with this Policy.

  * **Third Party Services.** We use outside vendors and services to help us better understand how users interact with our website, and to provide services to us or to you on our behalf. These third parties may have access to your personal information for use solely in connection with these authorized business activities.
  * **Business Transfer.** We may transfer your personal information to a third party if we or any of our affiliates are involved in a corporate restructuring (e.g., a sale, merger, or other transfer of assets).
  * **Affiliates.** We are a member of the Rightside Group, Ltd. family of companies (the “Family of Companies”). The Family of Companies includes the following U.S. based companies: Acquire This Name, Inc.; DomainSite, Inc.; eNom, Incorporated; eNom1039, Inc.; eNom1040, Inc.; eNom623, Inc.; eNom625, Inc.; Hot Media, Inc.; Mobile Name Services Incorporated; Name.com, Inc.; Name.net, Inc.; Name104, Inc.; Name105, Inc.; Name106, Inc.; Name107, Inc.; Name108, Inc.; Name109, Inc.; Name110, Inc.; Name111, Inc.; Name112, Inc.; Name113, Inc.; Name114, Inc.; Name115, Inc.; Name116, Inc.; Name117, Inc.; Name118, Inc.; Name119, Inc.; Name120, Inc.; Rightside Group, Ltd.; Rightside Operating Co.; Secure Business Services, Inc.; Sipence, Incorporated; Vedacore.com, Inc.; and Whois Privacy Protection Services, Inc. The Family of Companies also includes the following non-U.S. based companies: Bejing United TLD Tech Co., Ltd.; DMIH Limited; eNom Canada Corp.; Rightside Australia Pty Ltd; Rightside Canada, Inc.; Rightside Domains Europe Limited; and United TLD Holdco Ltd. We may share personal information with our members of the Family of Companies. Any use of your information by members of the Family of Companies is subject to this Policy or another policy no less protective of your privacy. Conversely, we may obtain information about you from members of the Family of Companies. Each U.S. based member of the Family of Companies adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles (as discussed below).
  * **Compliance and Safety.** We may disclose personal information when we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal or fraudulent activity or to protect the safety, rights, or property of us, our users, or others. We may also disclose personal information when we believe release is appropriate in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; enforce or apply our agreements; or protect our rights, property, or safety, our users, or others.

**Information Retention.**

We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information without notice, unless the law specifically requires otherwise. You must keep your own, separate back-up records. If you choose to permanently delete personal information from your account, back-up copies may exist for a short time in our databases.

**Information Security.**

On our side, we have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in place to help safeguard your information. However, neither people nor security systems, even encryption systems, are foolproof. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If the law imposes any non-disclaimable duty to protect your personal information, intentional misconduct will be the standard used to measure our compliance with that duty.

On your side, YOU MUST DO WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. You should protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer and sign off when finished if you are using a shared computer. We will not ask for passwords in an email, so if you get such a request, assume it is fraudulent. We also advise you not to disclose any information in public areas of our website that you do not wish to share, as it can be viewed and possibly used by others.

##### 3\. YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES

We want to highlight the ways you can take control of your privacy at Hot Media. We urge you to explore these options and choose the level of privacy at which you are most comfortable.

**Account Preferences.**

As a registered user, you can edit your account settings and information at the point of sign-in for each respective website. You also can delete your account if you choose.

**Marketing Preferences.**

Users can also unsubscribe from our newsletters or opt out of receiving emails (such promotional emails) by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email or newsletter. However, occasionally we may need to send you customary business communications such as website and administrative notices and confirmation emails, which you may not opt out of.

**Cookies.**

You can follow your browser’s instructions to remove cookies at any time. However, please be aware that if cookies are disabled or removed, our website may not function or appear as designed.

##### 4\. ADDITIONAL TERMS

**Identity Theft.**

If you believe that you are a victim of identity theft entitled by law to request information from us, contact us at our Legal Notice address below and we will let you know what additional information you must provide to us.

**Notice Required by Law.**

Where permitted by law, if we are required to disclose or provide notice of invasion of certain security systems, we will do so by email to the most current email address you have provided us.

**California Privacy Rights**

Residents of California who have an established business relationship with us may obtain certain information about the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, as well as the names and addresses of those third parties and examples of the types of services and products they market. To request a copy of this information disclosure, email us at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co) and we will respond within 30 days.

**FOR EUROPEAN UNION OR SWITZERLAND CITIZENS.**

Hot Media complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Hot Media has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

Note that you have the right to access, correct, or delete your personal data processed by Hot Media. Some personal data can be accessed, corrected, and deleted through your account. For assistance with accessing, correcting, or deleting your personal data, please contact us at legalnotice@rightside.co. Please be aware that deleting your personal data may result in termination of the services you receive through Hot Media.

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Hot Media commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Policy should first contact our parent company, Rightside Group, Ltd., at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co), or by postal mail at: Rightside Group, Ltd., Attn: Legal Department, 5808 Lake Washington Blvd NE, Suite 300, Kirkland, WA 98033 USA 

Hot Media has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for more information and to file a complaint. In addition, it is possible, under certain limited conditions, for individuals to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the US Department of Commerce and the European Commission. Note that the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has enforcement authority over Hot Media’s compliance with this Policy.

US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework

Hot Media complies with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland. Hot Media has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity and purpose limitation, access, and recourse, enforcement and liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the US-Swiss Safe Harbor and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

In compliance with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Hot Media commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Policy should first contact our parent company, Rightside Group, Ltd. at: [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co), or by postal mail at: Rightside Group, Ltd., Attn: Legal Department, 5808 Lake Washington Blvd NE, Suite 300, Kirkland, WA 98033 USA. 

Hot Media, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Hot Media, Inc., please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information and to file a complaint.

##### 5\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about privacy at Hot Media please email us at: [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co). To send us a legal notice, mail it by certified mail (return receipt requested) to: Rightside Group, Ltd., Attn: Legal Department, 5808 Lake Washington Blvd NE, Suite 300, Kirkland, WA 98033.

We will contact you, including when we give a legal notice, at an email address that we have on file for you.

Hotkeys, the Hotkeys logo, and Hot Media are trademarks and/or registered trademarks in the United States and/or other countries.
